[
    {
        "front": "かんがえます ||",
        "back": "think, consider",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "つきます |",
        "back": "arrive",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "とります |\n[としを～]",
        "back": "grow old",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "たります ||",
        "back": "be enough, be sufficient",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "いなか ",
        "back": "countryside, hometown",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "チャンス",
        "back": "chance",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "おく",
        "back": "hundred million",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "もし [～たら]",
        "back": "if",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "いみ",
        "back": "meaning",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "もしもし",
        "back": "hello (used on the phone)",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "てんきん",
        "back": "transfer (～します: be transgerred to another office)",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "こと",
        "back": "thing, matter (～の　こと:  thing about ~)",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "ひま",
        "back": "free time",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "[いろいろ]　おせわに　たりました。 ",
        "back": "thank you for everything you've done for me",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "がんばります |",
        "back": "do one's best",
        "chapter": 25
    },
    {
        "front": "どうぞう　おげんきで。",
        "back": "please take care of yourself. (said when expecting a long separation)",
        "chapter": 25
    }
]